Guide to the Theatre Festivals Collection, 1935-2012 SPEC.TRI.0013
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
Theatre Festivals Collection
1935-2012
SPEC.TRI.0013
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
7.85 Cubic feet
The Theatre Festivals Collection contains programs, advertising materials, and ephemera from domestic and international (mainly European) theatre festivals. Many theatre festivals have been established to promote various types of theatre or to promote the work of beginning playwrights and performers.
(19) 5" letter document boxes; (1) 2.5" legal document box
Jerome Lawrence and Robert E. Lee Theatre Research Institute.
Arrangement of Materials
The materials are arranged alphabetically by name of festival.
Acquisitions Information
Unknown
Access to Materials
Materials in this collection are available for use, but may be used in the Thompson Library Special Collections reading room only.
Historical Note
Numerous theatre festivals have been established to promote various types of theatre, such as the works of Shakespeare or George Bernard Shaw. Many festivals, such as fringe festivals, promote the work of beginning playwrights and performers.
Scope and Contents
The Theatre Festivals Collection contains programs, advertising materials, and ephemera from domestic and international (mainly European) theatre festivals. The materials date from 1935 to 2012.
Drama festivals--20th century; Drama festivals--21st century; Promotional materials; Theater programs
- Adelaide Festival, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- African Street Festival, 1992 July 21 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Alabama Shakespeare Festival, 1987-2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- American College Theater Festival, 1996 April (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The American Music Theatre Festival, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Ann Arbor Summer Festival, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Ann Arbor Summer Festival, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Annual Avignon Festival of International Theatre, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Annunciation Greek Orthodox Cathedral, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Artistry in Motion: Drum & Bugle Corps Competition, 1998 June 16 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- The Association of American Community Theatres Festival, 1989,1997 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Athen's Festival, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Avignon Festival, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Bach Festival, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Bayreuther Festspiele, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Belfast Festival, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- The Berlin Festival, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Berkshire Theatre Festival, 1952-2004 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Bernstein, Leonard Festival, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Boston Arts Festival, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Bristol Renaissance Faire, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Blyth Festival, 1986, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Buckeye Invitational, 1998 August 21-22 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Cameo, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Carnevale Teatro '8o, 1980 February (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Champlain Shakespeare Festival, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Champlain Shakespeare Festival, 1972-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Charlottetown Festival, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Chicago International Theatre Festival, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Chicago Renaissance Faire, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Colorado Shakespeare Festival, 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Columbus Arts Festival, 1990-1993 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Columbus Jewish Film Festival, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Columbus Mime/Clown Festival, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Columbus National Gay and Lesbian Theatre Festival, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Columbus Quincentennial Jubilee, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Czech Theater Festival, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Deutsche Theater und Festspiele, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Dublin Theatre Festival, 1965-1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Ecofestival, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Edinburgh Festival of Music and Drama, 1963-1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Edinburgh International Fringe Arts Festival, 1989-1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- The Empire State Music Festival, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Everybody's Shakespeare International Festival, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Festival 70, 1971 March 12- April 18 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Festival 2000, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Festival of Arts and Pageant of the Masters, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Festival of the Arts, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Festival d'Avignon, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Festival Casals, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Festival of Contemporary Arts, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Festival of Contemporary Music, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Festival of the Creative Arts, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Festival of First Stage Musicals, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Festival of India, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Festival Latino, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Festival of London, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Festival Materials Reports, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Festival of New British Theatre, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Festival Off, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Festival of Puppet Theatre, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Festival of Sydney, 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Festival Theatre at Rock Kiln Ruin, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Festival of Trees, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Festival of World Theatre, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Finn Fest, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- First Hispanic Play Festival, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- The First New York International Festival of the Arts, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Fringe Festival (Hollywood), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- German Festivals, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- German Festivals of the 17th and 18th Century Report, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Goodwill Arts Festival, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Great George Festival, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Great Lakes Region American College Theatre Festival, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Greater Columbus Arts Festival, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Greater Columbus Arts Festival, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Hamilton Fine Arts Festival, 1964-1969 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Hasidic Song Festival, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Holmoes County Antique Festival, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Homeless Theatre Festival (Annual), 1989 September 5 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Humana Festival, 1991, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Ibsen Festivalen, 1998 August 27-September 5 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Illinois Shakespeare Festival, 1980-1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- International Festival of the Art Song, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- International Festival of the Arts, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- International Festival of Puppet Theatre, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- International Senior Theatre Festival, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- International Theatre Festival of Chicago, 1986-1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Iowa Playwright's Festival, 1986-1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Kenyon Festival Theatre, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Lake Whalom Playhouse, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Lancaster Festival, 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Lincoln Center Festival, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Lincoln Center Festival, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lincoln Center Festival, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Ljubijana, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- London International Festival of Theater, 1993-2001 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- London Mime Theatre, 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Los Angeles Festival, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Los Angeles Shakespeare Festival, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- The Mac Wellman Festival, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Mad River Festival, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Majestic Theatre, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Manhattan Punch Line's 6th Annual Festival of One-Act Comedies, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- May Day, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- MC98, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Michigan Shakespeare Festival, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Milwaukee Theatre Festival, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Mostly Mozart Festival, 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Movement Theatre International Festival, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- National Black Arts Festival, 1988-1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- National Festival of Canadian Theatre, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Nederlanders, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Neil Simon Festival, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Neofest Festival of the New Arts, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- New York Festival Latino, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- New York Historical Society, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- New Hope Festival, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- New York International Festival, 1988-1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- New York Japan Fest, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- New York Shakespeare Festival, 1958-1997 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- New York Shakespeare Festival, 1993-1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- New York State Theatre Festival, 1967, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- New York Video Festival, 2000 July 24 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- New Zealand Festival of the Arts, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Next Wave Festival, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Notting Hill Carnival, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Le Nouveau Theatre National de Marseille, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Nutmeg Theatre, 1974-1990 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- NY Drama Critics Circle, 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- OCTA, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Off-Off Loop Theatre Festival, 1966, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Ohio Alliance for Arts Education, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Ohio Arts Council, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Ohio Arts Council, 1991-2000 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- The Ohio Citizens Committee for the Arts, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Ohio Community Theatre Association, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Ohio Community Theatre Association, 1966-2003 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Ohio Drama Education Exchange (ODEE), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Ohio Fan Fare, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Ohio Mime Festival, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Ohio State Fair, 1970-1996 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Ohio Theatre Alliance, 1980-1993 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Ohioana Library Association, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Olympics Arts Festival, 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- O'Neill Theatre Center National Playwrights Conference, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1971-1978 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Orpheus Casting, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Padua Playwright's Festival, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Pan American Fiesta, 1951-1990 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Panhellenion Folk Festival of Greece, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Parti Gras, 1995 March 11 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Philadelphia Drama Guild, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Philadelphia Festival Theatre, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia Festival Theatre for New Plays, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Philadelphia International Theatre Festival for Children, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Pinter Festival, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Pittsburgh Performing Artists Foundation, 1984-1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Playbill, 1958-1999 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Playbill, 1988-2004 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Playbill, 1946-2001 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Players Incorporated, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Playwrights of Philadelphia Play Festival, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Portland Civic Theatre, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Prescott Park Arts Festival, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- The Ravina Festival Association, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Red River Annual, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Religious Festivals Report, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Renaissance and Court Festivals Booklists and Reports, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Renaissance Festivals Report, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Riverside Studio, 1980-1999 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Roanoke Spring Festival of Fine Arts, 1961 April 3-30 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Rodgers and Hammerstein Organization, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Rotary Club of Marion, 1975 September 16 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Russian Festival, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Saint John's Italian Festival, 1992 September 19-20 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Salzburg Festival, 1935, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- San Diego Theatre League, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Sarasota French Film Festival, 1991 November 14-18 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Satirical Subversives Festival, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Schenz Theatrical Supply, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Self-Expression Teen Theatre, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Shakespeare and Co., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Shakespeare Festival Committee of the Arts Council of Great Britain, 1956-1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Shakespeare Festival of Dallas, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Short North Business Association, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Short North Performing Arts Association, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Showboat Centennials, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Singapore Arts Festival (1), 2001 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Singapore Arts Festival (2), 2001 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Spoleto Festival, 1962, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Spoleto Festival USA, 1983, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Spoleto Festival USA, 1983-1992 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Spoleto Melbourne, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Spoleto-Rome, 1990 June 13 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Spring Dance Festival, 1991 May 21 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Spring Music Festival, 1954 May 15-16 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Stratford, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Stratford Festival, 1952-1973 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Stratford Festival, 1958-1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Stratford Festival, 1953-1965 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Stratford Festival, 1953-1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Stratford Festival, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Stratford Festival, 1967-1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Stratford Festival, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Stratford Festival, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Stratford Festival, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Stratford Festival, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Stratford Festival, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Stratford Festival Costume Designs, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Stratford (1), 2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Stratford (2), 2003 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Stratford (1), 2004 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Stratford (2), 2004 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Stratford (1), 2006 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Stratford (2), 2006 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Stratford (3), 2006 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Stratford Festival, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Stratford Festival, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Stratford Festival, 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Stratford Festival, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Stratford Festival, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Stratford Festival, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Stratford Festival, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Stratford Festival, 1988-2002 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Stratford Festival, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Stratford Festival, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Stratford Festival, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Stratford Festival, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Stratford Festival, 1994-1996 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Stratford Festival, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Stratford Festival, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Stratford Festival, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Stratford Festival, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Stratford Festival, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Stratford Festival, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Stratford Festival, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Stratford Festival, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Stratford Festival, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Stratford Festival, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Stratford Festival, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Stratford Festival (1), 2001 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Stratford Festival (2), 2001 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Stratford Festival, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Stratford Festival, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Stratford Festival (Fanfares), 1961-1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Stratford Festival (miscellaneous), 1962-1990 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Stratford Festival for the Student, 1986-2002 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Stratford Festival for the Students, 1990-1996 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Stratford Reviews, 1971-1985 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Stratford Shakespeare Festival (1), 2012 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Stratford Shakespeare Festival (2), 2012 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Stratford upon Avon, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Summer Art Festival, 1969, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Sydney Festival, 1989 November 22 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Teatro-Festival, 1990 July 17 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- The Texas Playwrights Festival, 1990-1994 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Theatertreffen (West Berlin), 1987-1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Theatre Festival Moscow-Leningrad, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Theatre of Nations Festival, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Theatre Roulette, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Theatre of the World, 1989 September 5 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Three Rivers Shakespeare, 1980-1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Three Rivers Shakespeare, 1986-1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Three Rivers Shakespeare, 1991-1994 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Thunder Bay Community Auditorium, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Unityfest, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Unity Fest, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Unity Theatre, 1990 January 28 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Utah Shakespeare Festival, 1989-2005 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Utah Shakespearean Festival, 1985-1994 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Viva Victoria Festival, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- William Inge Festival, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- William Inge Festival, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- William Inge Festival, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- William Inge Festival, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- William Inge Festival, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- William Inge Festival, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- William Inge Festival, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- William Inge Festival, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- William Inge Festival, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- William Inge Festival, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- William Inge Festival, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- William Inge Festival, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- William Inge Festival, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- William Inge Festival, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- William Inge Festival, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- William Inge Festival, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- William Inge Festival, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- William Inge Festival, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- William Inge Festival, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- William Inge Festival, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- William Inge Festival, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- William Inge Festival, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- William Inge Festival: Ing Theatre, 1975, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- William Inge Festival: Inge (William) Obituary and Photograph, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- William Inge Festival: Press clippings, 1953-1972 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- William Inge Festival: Special Collection, 1981, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Winterfair, 1995-1997 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- The Worcester Drama Festival, 1946-1950 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- World Theatre Festival, 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Yale Drama Festival, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Yeats Festival, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Young Playwright Festival, 1989-1993 (Box 16, Folder 19)